Finding Aid for the Allegra Fuller Snyder papers, 1960-2010 LSC.1881
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Performance Programs., 1940-2010
  - Performance Programs-1979 (2 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 5)
    UCLA Resident Theater Company "The Tempest." Lynn Dally and Dancers. "Bharata Natyam" by Medha Yodh. "Roots of Brazilian Music: Corpo Santo." UCLA 16th Annual Hugh O'Brian Acting Awards. U.C. Dance Theater Concert. Bella Lewitzky Dance Company. American Ballet Theatre.
  - Performance Programs-1980. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    UCLA Dance Company, Senior concerts, Royal Dancers and Musicians from Kingdom of Bhutan, "Asa Ilile Yoruba," Lorn MacDougal and Lee Connor. U.C. Dance Theater Concert. "Mother, Worker, Ruler, Witch: Cross-Cultural Images of Women." "Daunce an Antick Hay." "Holiday." The Peking Opera.
  - Performance Programs-1981. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    "Bicentennial Celebration: Dance as Social and Popular Entertainment" by ADG and CORD. St. Paul The Apostle Parish "Advent Festival." Los Angeles Area Dance Alliance 3rd Annual Dance Kaleidoscope packet. See Box 64 for poster of UCLA Asian Performing Arts Institute presentation of "Noh."
  - Performance Programs-1982. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    UCLA Thesis concert. Two-Snake Dance and Design Company. Dance Ethnology Seminar with Richard Schechner. Jan., March, April "UCLA Center for the Performing Arts."
  - Performance Programs-1983. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Nov. Lincoln Center.
  - Performance Programs-1985. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Jerzy Grotowski. "Kei Takei's Moving Earth." "Ballett International." "Dance/LA Dance."
  - Performance Programs-1987. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    "Flamenco Puro." "Cabeza de Vaca: a ghost play in the style of Noh." John Huston's "The Dead."
  - Performance Programs-1988. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    "Asia & the American Indian: Mythology, shamanism and the arts." "Kwa- Gulth Dancers of Fort Rupert." Nov. "Performing Arts." "Soul of Japan" by Akiko Ishii Repertory Dance Group. "UCLA Dance Ethnology Forum: Presentation of papers and experiential workshops." June/July "Festivals." Booklet for "Bunraku: The national puppet theatre of Japan."
  - Performance Programs-1989 (1 of 2). (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Maria Benitez Spanish Dance Company. Jazz Tap Ensemble with Lynn Dally. "Synapse Dance Theater." "Anything Goes." "Jerome Robbins' Broadway." May "Performing Arts." "African Aesthetics in the Americas" sponsored by WAC.
  - Performance Programs-1989 (2 of 2). (Box 59, Folder 7)
    "Africa Oye!" "I Danzatori Scalzi." UCLA Dance Department Choreography & Performance Showcase. Oct. and Dec. "UCLA Center for the Performing Arts." American Ballet Theatre program and booklet with photos by Annie Leibovitz. Joffrey Ballet booklet and program.
  - Performance Programs-1990 (1 of 2). (Box 59, Folder 8)
    UCLA "Experiential Dimensions of Dance Ethnology," "The Practice or Art of Dancing." "Generator Eight." Synapse Dance Theater. "International Morris Dancing Ale." "Toes, Taps, and Top Hats." "Jazz Tap Ensemble" with Lynn Dally. "Amerika Maru." "Kabuki Dance Company." "Festival of Indonesia." "Forever Tango." "Fujima Fujiko: A living national treasure of Japan."
  - Performance Programs-1990 (2 of 2). (Box 59, Folder 9)
    UCLA Thesis concerts, Dance Company 25th Anniversary booklet and program. Feb., March, May "UCLA Center for the Performing Arts." "Avaz." "The Royal Court of Yogyakarta Java." Los Angeles Chamber Ballet. "Recontres Internationales de la Danse."
  - Performance Programs-1991 (1 of 2). (Box 60, Folder 1)
    "In the Works" presented by Dance Gallery. Wendy Osserman Dance Company. UCLA Senior concert, 12th Annual Dance Ethnology Forum, graduate program for WAC. Los Angeles Chamber Ballet flyer. "Memorial Celebration of the Life of Eleanor King." New York City Ballet.
  - Performance Programs-1991 (2 of 2). (Box 60, Folder 2)
    "Shakuntala" by Kalidasa. UCLA Thesis concert; "Kei Takei's Moving Earth in 24 Hour of Light;" Robert Allen, Nina Lucas, and Suzee Goldman; UCLA Dance Company; Bill T. Jones / Arnie Zane & Co. in "Last Supper at Uncle Tom's Cabin / The Promised Land." Winter "Aman Newsletter." "Frida Kahlo: A self-portrait in dance" by Priscilla Regalado. The Joffrey Ballet. International Documentary Association Oscar reception and film program. "Black Choreographers Moving Toward the 21st Century."
  - Performance Programs-1992. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    "DoWhatDo" by Joel Slayton program and bumper sticker. Craft and Folk Art Museum's "International Festival of Masks."
  - Performance Programs-1993. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    "Kerala Arts." Transitions Dance Company. Martha Graham Dance Company. UCLA "Sankai Juku," "Chongak and Eunyul Talch'um Traditional Music and Dance of Korea," "14th Annual Dance Ethnology Forum," "The Case for Display: Locating culture in festivals, museums and tourism." "Los Angeles Festival: Crossing LA Shockin' the house: Two decades of LA street dance." San Francisco Ethnic Dance Festival. International Documentary Association Oscar reception and film program.
  - Performance Programs-1994. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    UCLA "Revision Quests: Exploring the appropriation of Native American spirituality by non-natives," "15th Dance Ethnology Forum," Program on healing in Brazil by Yves Marton. "Performing Arts" for "Stomp," "Forever Tango," "Fool Moon."
  - Performance Programs-1995. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Jose Mateo's Ballet Theatre. "Performing Arts" for "The Joffrey Ballet of Chicago Nutcracker," Los Angeles Philharmonic," "Black Elk Speaks," "Lynn Redgrave Shakespeare for My Father."
  - Performance Programs-1996. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    "An Ideal Husband." "Performing Arts" for "Pina Bausch Tanztheatre Wuppertal," "Seven Guitars." Kenneth Branagh film "Hamlet." "Summer Nights at the Ford."
  - Performance Programs-1997. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    April "International Documentary" magazine. The Royal Ballet. "The Fosses."
  - Performance Programs-1998. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    "Performing Arts" for "Gross Indecency: The three trials of Oscar Wilde," "The Magic Flute," Mark Morris Dance Group, "Louis Bravo's Forever Tango," American Repertory Dance Company, "Bring in 'Da Noise, Bring in 'Da Funk." see also box 63, folder 4 for oversized booklet of "Bring in 'Da Noise, Bring in 'Da Funk."
  - Performance Programs-1999. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    "World Festival of Sacred Music-The Americas." Basil Twist's "Symphonie Fantastique." The musical "The Lion King." see also box 63, folder 5 for oversized booklets of Matthew Bourne's "Cinderella."
  - Performance Programs-2000. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    The Concord Ensemble in "The Stotsenberg Recital Series." Savion Glover in "Foot Notes: The concert." Los Angles Opera "Rigoletto."
  - Performance Programs-2001. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Lynn Dally's "Rhythm-a-ning" at Highways. Min Tanaka & Tokason in "Caprice: Guests from the dark." "Dance Kaleidoscope 2001."
  - Performance Programs-2002. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    "Loretta Livingston & Dancers and the Robin Cox Ensemble." "World Festival of Sacred Music-Los Angeles."
  - Performance Programs-2003. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    Meri Bender's "Dance Cycle" at Highways. "Anima / Animus." April-May "UCLAlive."
  - Performance Programs-2004. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    Oct. "UCLAlive." "An Evening of Dance with Yvonne Rainer and Simone Forti." June 19 and Oct. 23 "Jacaranda." Redcat's "Legend of Hip-Hop." Aloud at Central Library's "A Window on Movement and Language." "Thoroughly Modern Millie."
  - Performance Programs-2005. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    New York City Ballet. UCLA concerts "WAC is Back," Faculty Festival, WAC "M.F.A. Upstart Series," "Dance Under Construction VII: In/corp/orations." Savion Glover in "Improvography II." "World Festival of Sacred Music-Los Angeles." Feb. 26 "Jacaranda." Viver Brasil Dance Company's "Yabas / Queens." "A Long Bridge Over Deep Waters: The faith-based bridge show." Lynn Dally's "Jazz Tap Ensemble: Encore!" August Wilson's "Radio Golf." The Actor's Gang "Tartuffe."
  - Performance Programs-2006. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Oguri & Honeysuckle's "Caddy! Caddy! Caddy!" "R Dance Company's Freedom Dances" and "101" at Highways. "Eiko & Koma: Cambodian stories." Viver Brasil Dance Company's "Mo Ife: Love stories." Sam Shepard's "The God of Hell." "FITLA, International Latino Theatre Festival of Los Angeles." Film "The Brothers Quay."
  - Performance Programs-2007. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    "Man in the Belly of a Slaveship-From Angola to Angola" at Highways. Victoria Marks' "Not About Iraq." Nov. "UCLAlive" for "Sankai Juku" and Pina Bausch Tanztheater Wuppertal. Redcat's "Mill Morrison Theater of Decaying Memories." Polish Troupe "Teatr Zar." "Bunraku: The national puppet theatre of Japan." "Slow Dancing" at the Music Center.
  - Performance Programs-2008. (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Feb. "UCLAlive Onstage." "Bridge: Choreographic Dialogues" by UCLA Center for Intercultural Performance. "Forever Flamenco" with Jose Tanaka. Jacaranda presents "The Om Century, Part II-Lucidity."
  - Performance Programs-2009 (1 of 2). (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Jan. / Feb. "The Broad Stage." Jan. / Feb., April. / May / June, Nov. / Dec. "UCLAlive Onstage." Spring "UCLAlive Wire."
  - Performance Programs-2009 (2 of 2). (Box 62, Folder 6)
    CalArts Redcat performances "Jerome Bel: Pichet Klunchun and myself," "Locative Engima-Frameshape of hard mettles-A personal problem," "Dancing On Site and On Camera," "Anna Halprin / Anne Collod & Guests: Parades & changes, replays (2008)." "Cup of Java: Javanese dance voices" by UCLA Center for Intercultural Performance. Grotowski Institute "Institut Im. Jerzego Grotowskiego." "Jude Narita & Friends." Jacaranda presents "Rothko, Einstein & Grace" and "The Om Century, Part II - Sacrifice."
  - Performance Programs-2010. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Jacaranda presents "Rocking," "Licorice & Rosin," "Prussian Blues." "Chime Live!" Geffen Playhouse "Love, Loss, and What I Wore." "W;t" by Panndora Productions. "The 19th Annual Lester Horton Dance Awards." UCLA WAC "Unleashing Voices." "Los Angeles Public Library Awards Dinner." Highways "Los Angeles Poverty Department's Examination of the Personal and Social Costs of Incarceration in the U.S.," "Conversation Piece," "Perezian Geometry: A birthday celebration for Rudy Perez."
  - Performance Programs-Oversized 1966. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Bunraku: The Japanese puppet theatre booklet.
  - Performance Programs-Oversized 1966. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Murray Louis booklet.
  - Performance Programs-Oversized 1969. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Kabuki booklet.
  - Performance Programs-Oversized 1998. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    "Bring in 'Da Noise, Bring in 'Da Funk" with choreography by Savion Glover booklet.
  - Performance Programs-Oversized 1999. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Matthew Bourne's "Cinderella" booklet.
  - Performance Programs-Poster., 1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Poster of UCLA Asian Performing Arts Institute presentation of "Noh."
- Research Materials and Organizations Files., 1960-2010
  Alphabetically then chronologically organized, this is a collection of files that illustrate the research interests of AFS including dance, dance ethnology, dance on film, and dance therapy. It also includes materials associated with her membership in a large number of organizations. The products (presentations, lectures, articles, descriptions of films, photos, audio tapes) from her research and organization memberships are included as part of this series. There are substantial files that address the years that AFS was active with CORD and serving as a panelist for NEA. Her research with the Yaqui Indians and dance preservation and education through film are represented. The readings, materials, and student work for the courses that AFS taught in Dance, Ethnic Arts, and World Arts and Cultures are included, here.
  - African Humanities Institute., 1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Zulu Program handbook, Fall quarter.
  - AMAN Institute., 1980 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    "New England Contras: Syllabus supplement," January 25-26 by Harry Brauser.
  - American Association for Health, Physical Education and Recreation (AAHPER) and the California Association (CAHPER)., 1967-1974 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Catalog booklet for 89th anniversary National Convention. Correspondence for the Dance Division. Binational Dance Conference at University of Waterloo, 1971. CAHPER 1967 conference correspondence and program.
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW)., 1968-1971 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Correspondence requesting AFS to write an article for AAUW Journal special edition "Peace Bomb" and to film Mary-Averett Seelye. May 1968 "AAUW Journal."
  - American Dance Festival (ADF)., 1984-1990 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Correspondence and information packet for the 1990 ADF "The Black Tradition in American Modern Dance."
  - American Dance Guild (ADG)., 1974-1996 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    Correspondence. 1979 and 1981 membership lists. Fall/Winter 1996 "American Dance." Oct. 1976 and Dec. 1979/Jan 1980 "American Dance Guild Newsletter." See also Box 87, folder 6 National Dance Guild (NDG).
  - American Dance Therapy Association (ADTA)., 1971-1984 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    "The Creative Arts Therapist: A modern medicine man" by Eileen Lawlor. "The Healing Power of Dance Therapy" 18th Annual ADTA conference, 1983 program. Correspondence. "Dance Therapy… Focus on Process" 15th Annual ADTA conference, 1980 program and AFS opening address. 1976-1977 membership list. Dec. 1971 "ADTA Newsletter."
  - American Ethnological Society., 1989 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - American Folklore Society., 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    1979 annual meeting program, membership directory, Legacy Books catalog. Puppetry conference sheet.
  - Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences., 1983 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    11th International Congress program.
  - Anthropos 88., 1988 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    International Festival of Documentary Film program.
  - Art of Dance and Deaf., 1984 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    UCLA Center for the Performing Arts letter to AFS thanking her for participating.
  - Arts in Education-Coming to Our Senses., 1978 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    Correspondence and program concerning the Los Angeles City / County conference about the significance of the arts for American education.
  - Asia and the American Indian-Asia Society., 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    Symposium and festival of mythology, shamanism, and the arts. Correspondence and photocopies of newsclippings.
  - Asian Performing Arts Summer Institute (APASI)., 1981 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    The Classical Performing Arts Friendship Mission of Japan informational packet.
  - Association of American Dance Companies (AADC)., 1971-1974 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Meeting minutes, progress reports, and conference programs. California Arts Commission and AADC "The California Dance Directory: Fall 1972."
  - The Association for the Anthropological Study of Play (TAASP)., 1979-1983 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    "Reunion du Mardi Gras" 1983 preliminary program. Fall 1979 and fall 1982 "TAASP Newsletter."
  - Association for Women's Active Return to Education., 1968-1970 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    AWARE International Third Anniversary Jubilee program. "Evening Outlook" May 1968 newsclipping with photo of AFS.
  - Barnard College-Western Dance History., 1979 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    AFS papers for Western Dance History conference on film. Resources and teaching methods conference schedule.
  - Biographical Material, AFS-1960s., 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    Correspondence about AFS application to UCLA master's degree program. Franklin D. Murphy letter to applicants to graduate programs.
  - Biographical Material, AFS-1970s (1 of 2)., 1964-1980 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Articles about and by AFS. "Data Summary for Professorial Advancement." Biography, CV, statement letter. Letters of recognition from organizations for AFS participation. Two undated Polaroid family photos.
  - Biographical Material, AFS-1970s (2 of 2)., 1976-1979 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Newsclippings about AFS. "Interview with Allegra Snyder: Movement therapy: Reconciling mind and body."
  - Biographical Material, AFS-1980s (1 of 3)., 1985-1989 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    AFS Data Summary for Professorial Advancement. Newsclippings.
  - Biographical Material, AFS-1980s (2 of 3)., 1981-1984 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Newsclippings about or by AFS. Sept. 1981 "Dancemagazine." May 9, 1982 Los Angeles Herald Examiner article about Allegra and Robert Snyder "An Artful Compromise."
  - Biographical Material, AFS-1980s (3 of 3)., 1982 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    L.A. Weekly article "The Allegra Fuller Snyder Dance" by Judith Auberjonois. Two interview tapes and transcriptions.
  - Biographical Material, AFS-1990-2001., 1992-2001 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    "Metropolis 20th Anniversary Issue" article "Allegra Fuller Snyder." Biography, list of presentations, commendations.
  - Bolm, Adolph., 2002 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Chronology of Adolph Bolm. Photocopied photos of Bolm. Photomontage page of interview held at AFS home.
  - Brain Mind Bulletin (1 of 2)., 1977-1989 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Aug. 1986, May-Dec. 1988, Jan.-Aug. 1989 "Brain Mind Bulletin." Vol. I, 1977-vol. IX, 1984 "Brain Mind Theme Pack: Learning, education, creativity, suggestology, learning disorders."
  - Brain Mind Bulletin (2 of 2)., 1981-1985 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Vol. I, 1981-vol. V, 1985 "Leading Edge Bulletin Theme Pack: Learning/education." Vol. I, 1977-vol. IX, 1984 "Brain Mind Theme Pack: Mind/ Consciousness, physics, holography theories." Vol. I, 1977-vol. IX, 1984 "Brain Mind Theme Pack: Right/ Left hemisphere specialization."
  - California Confederation of the Arts (CCA)., 1978-1982 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    "Third Annual Congress of the Arts: Political impact of the arts." July 1982 "CCA Bulletin." Nov./Dec. 1981 and spring 1982 "CCA Newsletter." March 1981 "Advocacy Memo." March 1980, May/June 1980, Sept./Oct. 1980, and Nov./Dec. 1980 "Art Matters." Aug. 1978 "Los Angeles Arts View."
  - California Dance Educators Association (CDEA) 1970s., 1974-1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    1976 conference program. Fall 1974; Feb./March, Aug. 1977; March, June, summer, fall 1978; and winter-spring, fall 1979 "CDEA Newsletter."
  - California Dance Educators Association (CDEA) 1980s., 1980-1988 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    CDEA programs for honors Alma Hawkins, Marian van Tuyl, Gloria Unti. Winter, spring, summer 1980 and fall 1988 CDEA newsletter.
  - California Teachers Association (CTA)., 1966-1967 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Fine Arts Conference program. Winter 1966 / 1967 "The Valuator."
  - China Trip., 1982 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Itinerary and promotional material about tour to China with AFS serving as an advisor.
  - Colorado Dance Festival (CDF)., 1987 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    "A Moveable Feast" registration forms.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1960s., 1966-1969 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Programs, minutes, bylaws. Judith Lynn Hanna articles on African dance. Also known as Committee on Research in Dance.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1970. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, minutes.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1971. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, minutes, agendas. Membership list.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1972 (1 of 4). (Box 68, Folder 9)
    Board of Directors minutes, budgets, correspondence. Anya Peterson Royce CV. "The Role of the Dance Societies in the Easter Ceremonies of the Yaquis at Pascua" by Dawn M. Tooney.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1972 (2 of 4). (Box 68, Folder 10)
    List of people who did editorial work on "Impulse" 1951-1970. "Dance Research Monograph One 1971-1972." Third conference program. Correspondence. Submitted articles.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1972 (3 of 4). (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Correspondence and related material from Jan. and Feb.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1972 (4 of 4). (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Biographical data for 1972 nominees. 1971-1972 membership list. NEH grant application for "New Dimensions in Dance Research: Dance and anthropology." Tucson Creative Dance Center brochures.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1973 (1 of 2). (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Financial report. Correspondence. Reports and meetings information.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1973 (2 of 2). (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Correspondence. Reports and meetings information. Officer guidelines.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1974 (1 of 3). (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Membership list as of Dec. 1974. Guidelines for nominating committee. Bylaws. Correspondence. Sept. 16 "Extension Media Center: Lifelong Learning." CORD and Society for Ethnomusicology.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1974 (2 of 3). (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Correspondence. Applications to Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines for funding for CORD publications. Budget, annual meetings information, brochure.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1974 (3 of 3). (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Correspondence. American Folklore Society annual meeting program. National Science Foundation application "Anthropology and Dance." NEH grant application "CORD-SEM Dance Anthropology Conference." Membership directory. 1974 IRS 990.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1975 (1 of 5). (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, minutes, budgets, guidelines. Publications report for "Dance Research Journal."
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1975 (2 of 5). (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, bylaws, financial report, guidelines for publications.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1975 (3 of 5). (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, reports, financial report.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1975 (4 of 5). (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, financial report, bylaws.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1975 (5 of 5). (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Correspondence. 1975 IRS 990. Membership lists. "Media Anthropologist Newsletter." Winter "The Association for the Anthropological Study of Play Newsletter."
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1976 (1 of 4). (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Board of Director meetings. Correspondence, briefing reports, agenda, minutes. AFS past-President resignation acceptance. July "The International Congress of Physical Activity Sciences 1976" registration. "Interviews with Leaders in Education, the Arts, and Arts Education" by Charles B. Fowler.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1976 (2 of 4). (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Biographical data 1976 nominees. Budgets, agendas, correspondence, minutes, reports. Philadelphia fifth biennial conference preparation. Committee on Movement Studies correspondence.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1976 (3 of 4). (Box 72, Folder 1)
    "Dance Research Journal" budget. Correspondence, reports. AFS letter outlining major changes for coming years.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1976 (4 of 4). (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Annual elections. March membership list. Ruth Lert CV packet.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1977. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Summary of decisions affecting the general membership.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1978. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    "Levels of Event Patterns: An attempt to place dance in a holistic context" speech and contract. Conference registrants. Festival of Ethnic Music & Dance and Hawaii Dance Theatre brochures. Newsclippings and flyers. Summer "Bridge: An Asian American perspective." The contents of this file reflects AFS's original order.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) 1980s., 1981-1988 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, meeting minutes. Membership lists. Annual conference information. Publication listings. "European Perspectives in Structural Analysis of Dance" by A. Giurchescu. Yang Mei Qi of Guangdong Dance Academy speech.
  - Congress on Research in Dance (CORD) / American Dance Guild (ADG) Joint Conference., 1981 (Box 72, Folder 6)